Cute.
He's pulling it out of the out.
He's being licked.
They're pulling out high school kids.
They're so easy to fool, aren't they?
They're so easy to take, aren't they?
It's true! It's true! It's true! Strong one!
So, what are you doing today?
Well, we don't have any substitutes today, but we'd like to give you a little preview of what's in store.
Next up, the relay showdown!
Okay, Boifly, Fu-chan, please!
Please cheer for the winners, the older ladies or the high school students!
Now, the relay, please!
After this, we'll be splitting up into two groups, the sisters and the high school students, for the relay showdown!
I'm looking forward to this!
The high school team has 5 runners.
And since there are only 4 in the older lady's team
So, the older lady team needs to decide who will run one more lap.
I see.
When it's decided...
Uichan.
Who will run? The one with the fastest time is Takanashi.
What do you think?
That's what we'll do.
Okay, let's discuss and decide.
We can have others run in a row, right?
Maybe two in a row.
I'm not very good at starting.
Two laps in a row is tough.
It's a tough race, isn't it?I thought you said it was a tough game.
It's more like first and last.
One, four or two, four?
Which one?
The anchor is definitely Miri.
I was with either Rika or Haru.
That's where I rolled up.
The one in the middle is 1, 2, or 3?
Which do you think is better? Do you want to go with the middle one?
Reset it?
Or do I go the other way, put it in first and go after it?
The one you want to win.
In terms of time, which is faster, 1 or 2?
The middle?
Middle.
You haven't had that lately, have you?
What am I supposed to do?
I'd be afraid to be the first one to get three.
That's true.
Scary.
There's a difference between driving straight and taking a corner.
Two, three, four, five, six.
Five might be better.
I could have gone with five at first.
Five, I can't beat three.
Don't tell me it's the stars.
Five, three, four, five, six.
Five. I can't lose to three.
Don't tell me it's the stars' fault.
I won't let you say it's the stars.I won't let you say it.
the little guys
Fresh.
I really don't forgive
I won't allow it.
So, have you decided on the order?
High School Team
First layer.
Natsume, second layer.
Sasaki, third layer.
Nagamatsu, 4th layer
Fujisaki 5th layer
Hayashi
I see, I'll anchor and rewind at the end.
That's good.
And then, the elder sister's team
Hibino 2nd layer
Saito 3rd layer
Takanashi, 4th layer
Still there.
One more run on the 5th layer.
You mean run 3 and 5?
That's great. It was like the first and fifth layers.
Like 1 and 5.
I'm learning from experience that I'm not very good at starts.
I see. I've got 50 meters to go.
I wasn't very good at the start, even in club activities.
So I left it to Hame-chan to get me started.
Are you good at the start, Hibino?
I'm not good at the start.I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it, but they put me in charge anyway.
I thought I'd do my best anyway.
What do you think? We can't lose to the older girls' team or the high school team.
I won't let them beat me.
I get picked on a lot. They take a lot of crap from me.
The high school team is taking advantage of you?
We're going to show them that we're the big girls.
Tell them we're the better team.
Yeah, they're easy to take advantage of.
They're very easy to take.
I want to show them.
Against the high school team, ah, Hayashi was already sneering at them.
She was laughing at us, she's saying something.
Hayashi.
We can afford it.
She was saying.
That's good.
Now, and the high school team
Nagamatsu and Natsume may be a bit of a drag...
How about you, Natsume?
We'll be fine as long as we don't take the wrong course this time.
I'll do my best.
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
Nagamatsu.
I'm good at curves, so I'll be fine.
I'm good at curves.
That's great.
It's true.
You're an inventor.Invention.
Curve.
Inventive, isn't it?
Okay, well, let's go.
Okay, let's all get ready.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
How do you want to hand it, Mr. Button?
With your right hand?
You run with your right hand and pass it with your left.
Left hand?
Yes. - Okay.
Practice?
Can I do it?
You're number one.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
Okay, up or down.
Up. Up.
Up. Up. Up.
Which way do you want it?
There are idiots in here.
There's a moron in here.
I'll give it to you with my left hand.
Yes, sir.
Wait, it's not coming out.
Wait, you should put it a little lower when you give it to me.
Tell me.
Here.Here.
I'll give it to you here.
It's a short course.
It depends on whether it's an in-course or an out-course.
It changes a lot, doesn't it?
That's true.
You know what's funny?
It looks like the older sister's side is in.
I didn't know there were older sisters who didn't give in to younger sisters.
It makes me nervous.
It reminds me of a field day.
It's a field day.
I don't know why I remember it differently.
It reminds me of field day.
Come on!
Let's go! Come on! Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
All right, that's it, folks!
Here we go!
Are you ready?
Yes! Yes, please!
Let's go!
On your marks, come on!
Here we go!
Big sister's side is in the lead!
Now, that's the nut!
The curve!
Then corner the jujube!
Good luck, Natsume!
So the jujube is almost the slowest,Natsume is almost always the slowest,
So, you've already got Kime, right?
Now, the battle is on!
Natsume won the battle! Here we go!
The claw has hit!
We've got the claws!
The claws have hit!
Oh, he's obviously catching up.
Uh, he's catching up.
Uh...
Uh-oh.
He's passing him on the outside.
Oh, here comes Nagamatsu.
If it's Nagamatsu and Takanashi, that's it.
Nagamatsu has such a nice curve.
Nice curve!
It's still a little...
There's a curve behind us.
Don't let him get on the curve!
Curve!
Curve.
It's true. It's true.
It's true... he's good on curves.
Here they come. The baton has passed to Yoshimura and...
Yoshimura and Fujisaki.
Fujisaki's fast.
Yoshimura's pulling away.
Fujisaki's fast.Fujisaki early.
It's the anchor.
Last anchor.
Takanashi!
Come on, Takanashi, you're fast!
The baton's passed to the anchor!
Let's go! Let's run fast!
Takanashi in pursuit!
Let's run fast, Takanashi!
Takanashi, I'm chasing after you!
But you'd be surprised what a gap he's got!
Go, go, go, go!
The goal!
The winner was the high school team!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I'm crying!
I'm so moved!
Wait a minute. Stop for a second.
You're crying over this relay?
No, it moved me so much.
Now?
Everyone worked so well together.
Oh, I see.
I'm so proud of you guys for carrying the baton.
If I cried here, I'd be dead.
If I had a kid, I'd be dead.
I'd die if I had a kid in a relay or something.
Well, good job, everyone!Well, good job everyone!
That was a good game.
So, the results are
University student team 1:34.47
High school team: 1 minute 30.91 seconds
High school team won!
That was fast!
If it were 50m, my son would have been 2 or 3 seconds faster!
I couldn't pass the curve at all!
Curve!
A curve, a curve, a curve!
I'm still impressed every day!
I'm so impressed.
That's awesome!
That's amazing!
It means the high school team won!
The high school team won!
Yay!
It's true that you're really good at curving!
The curves were so fast!
The high school team was so cool.
Everybody looked good.
What is this guy?
How was it, Mr. Sakuma?
It was great, the teamwork.
I was very moved.
No tears, but...
No tears, but I was very moved.
Yes, it was a lot of things that happened.
I couldn't get emotionally involved.I didn't get too emotionally involved.
It was okay though.
It was a good competition.
Everyone was on top of their game.
No one was dragged down by anyone.
It was a good competition, wasn't it, Hibino?
It was a really good game.
The faster players covered for the slower ones.
And they couldn't go where they were supposed to go.
It was like watching a picture of an idol.
I see.
Hibino-san, that's what relays are all about.
But it's important for idols to help each other.
I could really feel it.
The person who is good at what they do first should do their best.
That's right, Saito.
Please don't do that.
I'm not good at what I'm good at.
You might not be good at progression, but...
You just have to fill in the blanks with that thing you're good at.
Like I told Semi
So you just do the best you can, and then
That's what you're going to get elsewhere
By people.
So we're all in this together doing it for the sake of it
We're not doing it alone.
It'll stick in your mind.
LOL.
You're right.As one would expect from a
Good job General.
I guess there are two this time
Sasaki and Nagamatsu?
Applause!
Sasaki, who pulled it off, and Nagamatsu, who was good at curving.
For sure.
Seriously, when he said he was good at curves
I don't know what he was talking about.
I did my training properly.
LOL!
Ok.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
This is gonna work.
It's gonna work.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Laughs.
I've been through a lot. I've been through a lot.
We've only got about five minutes left.
The future of riffraff depends on it here.
Oh, yeah.
I was right, wasn't I?
They're wonderful people.
Do you like cheering?
Do you like to cheer for those who cheer for you?
Do you like to be cheered?
Then I will!Then I'll support you!
Ready!
Yeah! Yeah! Oh!